Guide to the Department of Manuscripts and Archives, Yale University, Administrative Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Richard V. Szary, head of Manuscripts and Archives, records, 1991-2006; Accession 2007-A-134
  - Connecticut organizations
    - Mailbox inventory, computer file (XML)
  - Project management
    - Mailbox inventory, computer file (XML)
  - rszaryEmail
    - Mailbox inventory, computer file (XML)
- Records of Kirsten Jensen, 1978-2001; Accession 2007-A-141
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2036.
  - A300 Project
    - Tercentennial Information, 1996-1997 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - UA Background, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Committee Meetings Minutes, etc:, 1988-1998 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Committee Information Infrastructure, 1998-1999 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Cataloging
    - Procedures
      - Archives Subject Terms, 1998-1999 (Box 1, Folder 5)
      - Computer Files/CD-ROMs (Box 1, Folder 6)
      - General, 1997-1999 (Box 1, Folder 7)
      - AV General, 1999-2000 (Box 1, Folder 8)
      - MICROFILM: General, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 9)
      - MICROFILM: Samples (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Records Photographs RUs (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Records RU 803, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Catalog
    - Records - RU Samples (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Records - Yale 7X Video Series (Pubs), 1979 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Committees - Digital Imaging Infrastructure, 1998-1999 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Committees - AV General, 1998-1999 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Exhibits
    - Saarinen, 2000-2001 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Buildings
      - Part I: Pope Plan, 1997-1998 (Box 1, Folder 19)
      - Part II: Memorial Quadrangle, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 20)
      - Part III: Sterling Library, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 21)
      - Part IV: HGS and Law School, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 22)
      - Part V: Residential Colleges, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Procedures General, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Grants
    - NFPF I
      - Class Films (Box 1, Folder 25)
        - Budget, 1998-1999 (Box 1, Folder 26)
        - Contract, 1998-1999 (Box 1, Folder 27)
        - Correspondence, 1998-1999 (Box 1, Folder 28)
        - Proposal, 1998-1999 (Box 1, Folder 29)
        - Publicity, 1998-1999 (Box 1, Folder 30)
        - Reports, 1998-1999 (Box 1, Folder 31)
        - Film List, 1998-1999 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - NPFP III
      - Files, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Media Design Studio
    - General Info, 1985-1989 (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - Siringo/Westering, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Microfilm
    - Budget, 1998-2000 (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - General, Leaflets, etc. (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - Procedures General, 1998-1999 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Preservation
    - Budget Information, 1998-1999 (Box 1, Folder 43)
    - Materials Sent to Conservation, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 44)
    - Procedures General, Dept., 1999 (Box 1, Folder 45)
    - Vendors WRS, Non-Grant Work, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - SGML/EAD/Finding Aids
    - Conversion Project: RFP, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 47)
    - FrameMaker SGML, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 48)
    - General, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 49)
    - MSSA Templates and Styles, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Records Management: Miscellaneous Yale Schedules, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Obsolete publications manual, 1999-2001 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Administrative and financial records of the Department of Manuscripts and Archives, circa 1969-2006; Accession 2008-A-094
  - CORRESPONDENCE
    - General, 1969-1989 (Box 1, Folder 1 - 29)
    - Columbia University Consultant Study for Creation of University Archives, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - University Microfilm International, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - History of Science, 1976-1978 (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - Middle Eastern Collections and Exhibit, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - Pacific Manuscripts Bureau, 1976-1978 (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - Scientific and Technologies Program: MIT, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - VWV: Vietnam War Veterans', 1980 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - DEPARTMENT ADMINISTRATION
    - Full Staff Meetings, 1989-1992 (Box 1, Folder 39 - 41)
    - Senior Staff Meetings, 1989-1993 (Box 1, Folder 42 - 45)
    - Monthly Activity Report, 1992-1993 (Box 1, Folder 46)
    - Planning
      - Budget discussions, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 47)
      - Mission, goals, and objectives statement, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 48)
      - Departmental Organization, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 49)
      - Action Plan, 1994-1995 (Box 1, Folder 50)
      - Yale University Library Planning, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 51)
      - University Audit-Planning, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 52)
    - Program and Project Management
      - Proposals, Projects
        - Brewster Presidential Papers Project, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 57)
        - Kingman Brewster, Jr. Documentation Project, 1989-1992 (Box 1, Folder 58)
        - Yale University Music Library Oral History, America Music Proposal to NEH, Draft, 1989 August (Box 1, Folder 59)
        - Yale Serials Project, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 60)
        - Cushing Papers Planning Memos, Finding Aids, 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 61)
      - Department Grants and Projects
        - Latin American Pamphlets in the Yale Library, 1979-1982 (Box 2, Folder 62)
        - Material Culture Project in Manuscripts and Archives, 1979-1980 (Box 2, Folder 63)
        - Beinecke Discussions, 1968-1972 (Box 2, Folder 64)
        - China Records Project, 1968-1974 (Box 2, Folder 65)
        - Exhibits, Manuscripts and Archives, 1973-1978 (Box 2, Folder 67)
        - Exhibits: YU Architectural Drawings Exhibition, 1979-1982 (Box 2, Folder 68)
        - Family Papers Project (Proposed), 1973, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 69 - 70)
      - Department Grants and Projects (Non-Current)
        - Yale University Library Gazette Recent Acquisitions Column, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 71)
        - Council of Archives and Research Libraries in Jewish Studies (CARLJS) Archives Preservation Microfilming Project, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 72)
        - Medical History Collection Cushing and Fulton Estimates, 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 73)
        - Microfilm Budget, policy and Procedure, 1969-1974 (Box 2, Folder 74)
        - Microfilm Publication, 1971-1974 (Box 2, Folder 75)
        - Microfilm Publications of MSSA: YUL Publications Office, 1971-1974 (Box 2, Folder 76)
        - Jeffrey Norton Publishers W.F. Buckley Tapes, 1976-1995 (Box 2, Folder 77)
        - RLIN/AMC Workstation, Yale/RLG Proposal to Title IIC Nov, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 78 - 81)
        - Stimson Papers: Declassification, 1969-1973 (Box 2, Folder 82)
        - Stimson Papers: NHPRC Project, 1971-1973 (Box 2, Folder 83)
        - Yale College Seminar Program (J. Schiff) Timothy Dwight Evaluating 20's and 30's thru Lindbergh, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 84)
        - Yale College Seminar Program (T. Myrans) Saybrook CSSY 130a: Editing Historical MSS, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 85)
        - Yale Documentary Editing Course (History 485B, Tony Myrans), 1978 (Box 2, Folder 86)
    - University Archives
      - Microfilming, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 87)
      - Archives Microfilming, 1989-1991 (Box 2, Folder 88 - 89)
    - Fortunoff Archives for Holocaust Testimonies
      - 10thAnniversary, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 90)
      - Videotapes Preservation, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 91)
      - Coordination with the Library
      - YUL -Divinity Library, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 92)
    - Inter-Institutional and Professional Cooperation (Box 2)
      - South African Archivist, 1988-1992 (Box 2, Folder 93)
    - Community Relations
      - Axion Research, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 94)
    - Reader Services
      - Reader Services Patron Profiles, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 95)
      - Reader Services, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 96)
      - Reader Services -Duplication of Collection Materials, Videotapes, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 97)
    - Bibliographic Instruction
      - Enterprise, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 98)
    - Exhibits
      - Yale Tercentennial, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 99)
      - Exhibits -Amistad, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 100)
    - Departmental Publications
      - SML Exhibit, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 101 - 112)
    - Collection Definition
      - Collection Management Policy
        - Access Policy: Yale University Archives, Office Files and Student Records, 1969-1979 (Box 2, Folder 113 - 115)
        - Access Policy: Yale University Archives, Individual Cases, 1977-1985 (Box 2, Folder 116)
        - Administrative Data on MSS and Archives for Librarian's Office, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 117)
        - Appraisal and Disposal of Donate Property (IRS 8282, 8283), 1985-1992 (Box 2, Folder 118)
        - Appraisals, Yale University Library Policy Statement, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 119)
        - Appraisers American Society of, Directory, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 120)
        - Appraisers, List of, 1987-1993 (Box 2, Folder 121)
        - Appraisers, Herman Liebert, 1977-1981 (Box 2, Folder 122)
        - Deposit Agreement: Procedures and Policies, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 123)
        - Freedom of Information Act: Yale Library Project Request, 1977-1979 (Box 2, Folder 124)
        - Freedom of Information Act: Yale Request, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 125)
        - Freedom of Information Act: Yale Request 1981 -Kingman Brewster and other Yale Officials, 1970-1981 (Box 2, Folder 126)
        - Income Tax and Charitable Deductions, 1969-1981 (Box 2, Folder 127 - 128)
        - Manuscripts and Archives Advisory Committee (Collection Development), 1976 (Box 2, Folder 129)
        - Permission to Publish, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 130)
        - Photo duplication Report and Related Materials, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 131)
        - Yale University Archives: Archives and Records Management Program, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 132)
    - Preservation
      - RLG Film Projects, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 142)
      - Preservation -Videotapes, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 143)
      - Preservation -Microfilm to Digital Imagery, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 144)
      - Cataloging
      - Cataloging ORBIS/OPAC Screens, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 145)
    - Collecting Areas
      - Medicine, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 146)
      - Drama, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 147)
      - Microforms Transfer, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 148)
      - Dissertations, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 149)
      - Transfer from BRBL, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 150)
      - Processing: Collections needing work, 1975-1977 (Box 2, Folder 151)
    - Personnel
      - Personnel 1.3.1, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 152)
      - Administrative Travel Request, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 153)
      - Professional Travel, 2004-2005 (Box 3, Folder 154)
      - Staff: A/T Travel Requests, 2004-2005 (Box 3, Folder 155)
      - Professional Travel, 2005-2006 (Box 3, Folder 156)
      - Staff: A/T Travel Requests, 2005-2006 (Box 3, Folder 157)
      - Staff: Learning Plans, 2005-2006 (Box 3, Folder 158)
    - Miscellaneous
      - New England Archivists' Conference Local Arrangements, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 159 - 161)
      - Essential Services, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 162)
      - Equipment Request, 1995-1996 (Box 3, Folder 163)
      - ADMIN: Equipment Request, 2002-2003 (Box 3, Folder 164)
    - Reports
      - ORBIS Acquisitions Reports, 2004-2005 (Box 3, Folder 165)
      - ORBIS Acquisitions Reports, 2003-2004 (Box 3, Folder 166)
      - RLG RLIN Invoices, 2005-2006 (Box 3, Folder 167)
      - RLG RLIN Invoices, 2004-2005 (Box 3, Folder 168)
  - FINANCIAL RECORDS
    - FY 2003-2004
      - Budget, 2003-2004 (Box 3, Folder 169)
      - ADMIN - Budget - RLG, 2003-2004 (Box 3, Folder 170)
      - Special Collections-Departmental, 2003-2004 (Box 3, Folder 171)
      - Special Collections-Archives, 2003-2004 (Box 3, Folder 172)
      - Library Books-Gifts, 2003-2004 (Box 3, Folder 173)
      - Library Books-Bullitt, 2003-2004 (Box 3, Folder 174)
      - Learning Plan, 2003-2004 (Box 3, Folder 175)
      - Kahn, 2003-2004 (Box 3, Folder 176)
      - GA-Archives, 2003-2004 (Box 3, Folder 177)
      - Fees and Fines-Departmental, 2003-2004 (Box 3, Folder 178)
      - Fees and Fines-Archives, 2003-2004 (Box 3, Folder 179)
      - E-RECS, 2003-2004 (Box 3, Folder 180)
      - Class of 1884, 2003-2004 (Box 3, Folder 181)
      - Bingham-Departmental, 2003-2004 (Box 3, Folder 182)
      - Architecture-General, 2003-2004 (Box 3, Folder 183)
      - Shoah, 2003-2004 (Box 3, Folder 184)
      - IDT, 2003-2004 (Box 3, Folder 185)
      - Gale, 2003-2004 (Box 3, Folder 186)
      - Gale Royalty Statements, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 187)
    - FY 2002-2003
      - IDT, 2002-2003 (Box 3, Folder 188)
      - Photocopy: Deposit/RIF, 2002-2003 (Box 3, Folder 189)
      - Bingham Departmental 0032728.00.29402A.xxxxx.802001, 2002-2003 (Box 3, Folder 190)
      - Buckley Tapes 0032728.00.51563A.xxxxx.802001, 2002-2003 (Box 3, Folder 191)
      - Class of 1884 0032728.00.27547A.xxxxx.802001, 2002-2003 (Box 3, Folder 192)
      - Vance 0032728.00.55138A.xxxxx.802001, 2002-2003 (Box 3, Folder 193)
      - Syz 0032728.00.50579A.xxxxx.802001, 2002-2003 (Box 3, Folder 194)
      - Yale Memorabilia 0032728.00.29155A.xxxxx.802001, 2002-2003 (Box 3, Folder 195)
      - Law Library Capital Campaign (Lg project) 0032728.00.55211A.xxxxx.802001, 2002-2003 (Box 3, Folder 196)
      - Kahn 0032728.00.28180A.xxxxx.802001, 2002-2003 (Box 3, Folder 197)
      - Special Collections Archives 0032730.00.29407A.xxxxx.802001, 2002-2003 (Box 3, Folder 198)
      - Special Collections Departmental 0032728.00.29407A.xxxxx.802001, 2002-2003 (Box 3, Folder 199)
      - Library Books (Gifts, General) 0036693.00.51577A.xxxxx.802001, 2002-2003 (Box 3, Folder 200)
      - Library Books (Latin America), 2002-2003 (Box 3, Folder 201)
      - Fees and Fines Archives 0026031.00.0061BC.xxxxx.802001, 2002-2003 (Box 3, Folder 202)
      - GA Archives 0032730.00.0001BC.802001, 2002-2003 (Box 3, Folder 203)
      - Photocopy 0026059.00.0061BC.xxxxx.802001, 2002-2003 (Box 3, Folder 204)
      - Current Use -Special Programs, Archives 0032730.00.0061BC.xxxxx.802001, 2002-2003 (Box 3, Folder 205)
      - Preservation Supply Questions, 2002-2003 (Box 3, Folder 206)
      - Gifts to MSSA, 2002-2003 (Box 3, Folder 207)
      - OTHER PTAEOs, 2002-2003 (Box 3, Folder 208)
    - 2001-2002
      - IDT, 2001-2002 (Box 3, Folder 209)
      - P-Card -Rich, 2001-2002 (Box 3, Folder 210)
      - Credit Cards, 2001-2002 (Box 3, Folder 211)
      - Ok to Pays, 2001-2002 (Box 3, Folder 212)
      - Photocopy Account, 2001-2002 (Box 3, Folder 213 - 214)
      - Photocopy: Deposit/RIF, 2001-2002 (Box 3, Folder 215)
      - Shipping Memorandums, 2001-2002 (Box 4, Folder 216)
      - Supplies, 2001-2002 (Box 4, Folder 217)
      - Univ. Arch GA 0032730.00.0001BC.xxxxx.802001, 2001-2002 (Box 4, Folder 218)
      - Library Books -Gifts 0036693.00.51577A.xxxxx.802001, 2001-2002 (Box 4, Folder 219)
      - 0032730.00.0001BC.850610.802003 MSSARCH02 -Orbis Fund Code, 2001-2002 (Box 4, Folder 220)
      - 1884 0032728.00.27547A.802001, 2001-2002 (Box 4, Folder 221)
      - 0032730.00.0061BC._____.802001 E-Recs, 2001-2002 (Box 4, Folder 222)
      - 0032728.00.55211A._____.802001 Law Library-Capital Campaign, 2001-2002 (Box 4, Folder 223)
      - Bingham Departmental 0032728.00.29402A._____.802001, 2001-2002 (Box 4, Folder 224)
      - Yale Memorabilia 0032728.00.39155A_____.802001, 2001-2002 (Box 4, Folder 226)
      - Lindbergh 0032728.00.28265A._____.802001, 2001-2002 (Box 4, Folder 227)
      - 0032728.00.28180A._____.802001-Kahn, 2001-2002 (Box 4, Folder 228)
      - 0032728.00.29407A-Special Collections, 2001-2002 (Box 4, Folder 229)
      - Completed Exhibit Info, 2001-2002 (Box 4, Folder 230)
      - Other Reimbursements, 2001-2002 (Box 4, Folder 231)
      - Orders for SEC - Archives -, 2001-2002 (Box 4, Folder 232)
      - PROF/Admin Travel, 2001-2001 (Box 4, Folder 233)
    - 2000-2001
      - IDT, 2000-2001 (Box 4, Folder 234)
      - Photocopy: Deposit/RIF, 2000-2001 (Box 4, Folder 235)
      - Supplies, 2000-2001 (Box 4, Folder 236)
      - Driggs 0032728.00.27690A, 2000-2001 (Box 4, Folder 237)
      - 0032728-00-51563A-802001 (Buckley Tapes), 2000-2001 (Box 4, Folder 238)
      - 0036693-00-51577A (Gift), 2000-2001 (Box 4, Folder 239)
      - 0032728.00.29407A.xxxxx.802001-Reconciled, 2000-2001 (Box 4, Folder 240)
      - 0032728.00.29402A.xxxxx.802001-Reconciled, 2000-2001 (Box 4, Folder 241)
      - 0026059-00-0061BC (Photocopy), 2000-2001 (Box 4, Folder 242)
    - 1999-2000
      - IDT, 1999-2000 (Box 4, Folder 243)
      - Supplies, 1999-2000 (Box 4, Folder 244)
      - Photocopy: Deposit/RIF, 1999-2000 (Box 4, Folder 245)
      - 0032728-00-0001BC (GA), 1999-2000 (Box 4, Folder 246)
      - 0032728-00-27547A (Class of 1884), 1999-2000 (Box 4, Folder 247)
      - 0032728-00-29407A (Office Supplies), 1999-2000 (Box 4, Folder 248)
      - 0032728-00-51566A-802001 (Buckley Papers), 1999-2000 (Box 4, Folder 249)
      - 0032728.00.28265A Lindbergh, 1999-2000 (Box 4, Folder 250)
      - 0032730-00-29402A-802003, 1999-2000 (Box 4, Folder 251)
      - UNKNOWN PTAEO, 1999-2000 (Box 4, Folder 252)
    - Special Project and Grant Accounts: 1978-1991
      - 802A-50-43749 Preservation and Subject Guide Project, 1978-1979 (Box 4, Folder 254)
      - 802A-50-43768 Preservation and Subject Guide Project, 1979-1980 (Box 4, Folder 255)
      - 802A-50-43787 Hew Title IIC Grant, 1980-1981 (Box 4, Folder 256)
      - 802A-50-43825 Dept of Ed Title IIC Grant Year II, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 257)
      - 802A-50-43843 USDOE Title IIC Grant, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 258)
      - 802A-50-43867 USDOE Title IIC Grant, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 259)
      - Title IIC extension 802A-50-43867, 1985-1988 (Box 4, Folder 260)
      - Title IIC Project Meeting Yale/Cornell/Stanford, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 261)
      - Yale, Stanford, Cornell, 1982-1985 (Box 4, Folder 262)
      - 802A-50-44978/44515 House Diaries, 1978-1979 (Box 4, Folder 263)
      - 802A-50-44525 (temp. 87999, 87981) University Records Survey, 1979-1980 (Box 4, Folder 264)
      - 802A-50-44991 Architectural Plans Project, 1979-1980 (Box 4, Folder 265)
      - 802A-50-47474 Contemporary Medical Care Year I, 1978-1980 (Box 4, Folder 266)
      - 802A-50-48070 Contemporary Medical Care Year II, 1979-1980 (Box 4, Folder 267)
      - 802A-50-48100 Contemporary Medical Care Year III, 1981-1982 (Box 4, Folder 268)
    - FY 1998-2003
      - Budget-Misc, 2000-2002 (Box 5, Folder 269)
      - Budget-Misc, 1998-1999 (Box 5, Folder 270)
      - Receipts [financial, miscellaneous], 2000-2002 (Box 5, Folder 271)
      - Sales Tax, 2000-2003 (Box 5, Folder 272)
      - Danka (Copier), 2000-2003 (Box 5, Folder 273)
      - Credit Cards -Discover, 2001-2003 (Box 5, Folder 274)
      - Credit Cards -American Express, 2001-2003 (Box 5, Folder 275)
      - Sales Tax -American Express, 2001-2003 (Box 5, Folder 276)
      - Credit Cards -Visa and Master Card, 2001-2003 (Box 5, Folder 277)
      - Sales Tax -Visa and Master Card, 2001-2003 (Box 5, Folder 278)
      - P-Card, 2001-2003 (Box 5, Folder 279)
      - Non-Departmental Accounts, 1998-2000 (Box 5, Folder 280)
      - 0032730-00-0061BC (Archives 300), 1999-2001 (Box 5, Folder 281)
      - 0032728-00-28180A (Herman Kahn), 1999-2001 (Box 5, Folder 282)
      - 0026031-00-0061BC (Lib. Fees and Fines), 1999-2001 (Box 5, Folder 283)
      - 0032728-00-55211A (Law Lib Capital), 1999-2001 (Box 5, Folder 284)
      - Travel Reimbursements, 1999-2001 (Box 5, Folder 285)
      - Employee Reimbursements, 1999-2004 (Box 5, Folder 286)
    - FY 2003-2006
      - Driggs, 2004-2005 (Box 5, Folder 287)
      - Kahn, 2004-2005 (Box 5, Folder 288)
      - Special Collections-Departmental, 2004-2005 (Box 5, Folder 289)
      - Yale Memorabilia, 2004-2005 (Box 5, Folder 290)
      - Dudley, 2004-2005 (Box 5, Folder 291)
      - Kelly, 2004-2005 (Box 5, Folder 292)
      - Saarinen, 2004-2005 (Box 5, Folder 293)
      - Library Books-Bullitt, 2004-2005 (Box 5, Folder 294)
      - Library Books-Gifts, 2004-2005 (Box 5, Folder 295)
      - Fedora, 2004-2005 (Box 5, Folder 296)
      - ERECS, 2004-2005 (Box 5, Folder 297)
      - Fees and Fines-Archives, 2004-2005 (Box 5, Folder 298)
      - Fees and Fines-Departmental, 2004-2005 (Box 5, Folder 299)
      - GA-Archives, 2004-2005 (Box 5, Folder 300)
      - Learning Plan, 2004-2005 (Box 5, Folder 301)
      - Photocopy, 2004-2005 (Box 5, Folder 302)
      - Public Services: Sales Tax, 2004-2005 (Box 5, Folder 303)
      - Public Services: Discover, 2004-2005 (Box 5, Folder 304)
      - Public Services: Deposits-VISA/MC, 2004-2005 (Box 5, Folder 305)
      - Public Services: AMEX, 2004-2005 (Box 5, Folder 306)
      - Photocopy, 2003-2004 (Box 5, Folder 307)
      - Public Services: Sales Tax, 2003-2004 (Box 5, Folder 308)
      - Public Services: Discover, 2003-2004 (Box 5, Folder 309)
      - PCard, 2003-2006 (Box 5, Folder 310 - 312)
      - Gale, 2004-2005 (Box 5, Folder 313)
      - Scholarly Resources, 2003-2005 (Box 5, Folder 314)
      - Budget and Finances: 2004-2005 Budget (Box 6, Folder 316)
      - Bingham Archives, 2005-2006 (Box 6, Folder 317)
      - Bingham Departmental, 2005-2006 (Box 6, Folder 318)
      - Class of 1884, 2005-2006 (Box 6, Folder 319)
      - Driggs, 2005-2006 (Box 6, Folder 320)
      - Kahn, 2005-2006 (Box 6, Folder 321)
      - Lindbergh, 2005-2006 (Box 6, Folder 322)
      - Special Collections-Archives, 2005-2006 (Box 6, Folder 323)
      - Special Collections-Departmental, 2005-2006 (Box 6, Folder 324)
      - Yale Memorabilia, 2005-2006 (Box 6, Folder 325)
      - Dudley, 2005-2006 (Box 6, Folder 326)
      - Nalle, 2005-2006 (Box 6, Folder 327)
      - Saarinen, 2005-2006 (Box 6, Folder 328)
      - Library Books-Bullitt, 2005-2006 (Box 6, Folder 329)
      - Discretionary-Law Library (Emerson), 2005-2006 (Box 6, Folder 330)
      - Fedora, 2005-2006 (Box 6, Folder 331)
      - GLBTQ-General, 2005-2006 (Box 6, Folder 332)
      - Law Library-Capital Campaign, 2005-2006 (Box 6, Folder 333)
      - Library Books-Gifts, 2005-2006 (Box 6, Folder 334)
      - Archives Services, 2005-2006 (Box 6, Folder 335)
      - E-RECS, 2005-2006 (Box 7, Folder 336)
      - Fees and Fines-Departmental, 2005-2006 (Box 7, Folder 337)
      - GA-Archives, 2005-2006 (Box 7, Folder 338)
      - Learning Plan, 2005-2006 (Box 7, Folder 339)
      - Royalties, 2005-2006 (Box 7, Folder 340)
      - Shoah, 2005-2006 (Box 7, Folder 341)
      - Public Services, 2005-2006 (Box 7, Folder 342)
      - Public Services: Sales Tax, 2005-2006 (Box 7, Folder 343)
      - Public Services: Deposits-VISA/MC, 2005-2006 (Box 7, Folder 344)
      - Public Services: AMEX, 2005-2006 (Box 7, Folder 345)
  - Videorecording of Alfred Van Sinderent donation of president's letters, undated; 1 (Box 8)
- University Archives accession files, 2006-2008; Accession 2009-A-105
  Restricted to office of origin only.
  - 2007-A-001 - 2007-A-110 (Box 1)
  - 2007-A-111 - 2007-A-233 (Box 2)
  - 2008-A-001 - 2008-A-105 (Box 3)
  - 2008-A-106 - 2008-A-193 (Box 4)
- University Archives accession inventories, circa 1980-1990; Accession 2010-A-035
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2026
  - YRG 3 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - YRG 4 (Box 1, Folder 2-6)
  - YRG 5 (Box 1, Folder 7-8)
  - YRG 32 (Box 1, Folder 9-13)
  - YRG 45 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- University Archives accession folders, 2008-2009; Accession 2011-A-014
  - 2009-A-001 -- 2009-D-102 (Box 1)
  - 2009-A-103 -- 2009-A-217 (Box 2)
- Records concerning the "Oral histories documenting Yale University women" project (RU 1051) under Florence Minnis, 1972-2010; Accession 2012-A-026
  Restricted until January 1, 2045
  Original born digital files, as well as preservation masters, may not be accessed due to their fragility. Researchers must consult use copies, or if none exist request that they be made. Born digital files cannot be accessed remotely. System requirements include a Manuscripts and Archives computer and file viewing software.
  - Bibliography (printed sources)
    - Books -- alphabetical, general, 2006-2010 (Box 1, Folder 1)